http://www.smithsflowers.com/privacy/

HomeShop for FlowersOccasionBirthdayAnniversaryGet WellJust BecauseLove/RomanceCongratulationsCelebrateThank YouThinking of YouI'm SorryNew BabyNew Home/OfficeWeddingChristmasSympathyFlower TypeSunflowerGerberaRosesLilyCarnationDaisyAlstromeriaTulipIrisHydrangeaCalla LilyOrchidBells of IrelandMumsColorYellowMixedPinkWhiteLavenderPurpleRedGreenOrangePastelPrimaryJewel TonesBluePlant TypeGreen PlantsDish GardensBlooming PlantPriceLess than 25From 25 to 40From 40 to 60From 60 to 100More than 100Shop for GiftsFruit/GourmetLocal ArtTeddy Bears & MorePlant AccessoriesBlossom SpringsResourcesFlower Care TipsFlower MeaningsThe Color of RosesYour Birth Month FlowerFAQsWedding Contact FormLinksContact UsBlog
Login
Register
×
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect? We collect
information from you when you register on our site, place an order,
subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When
ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked
to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or
credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: • To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)• To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)• To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)• To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be
sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any
reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express
purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
• To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, will
only be used
to send you information and updates pertaining to your
order.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future
emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of
each email.How do we protect your information? We
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or
access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure
server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment
gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized
with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the
information confidential.After a transaction, your private
information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.)
will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.Do we use cookies? Yes
(Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)
that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information We use
cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart
and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so
that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We
may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better
understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not
permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help
us conduct and improve our business.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party
products or services on our website. These third party sites have
separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no
responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these
linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site
and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause
we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in
compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We
therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside
parties without your consent.As part of the California Online
Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to
their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and
going to the 'Edit Profile' page.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We
are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online
Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If
we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on
this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on Sep 8, 2010Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. www.demoflowershop.com250 The East Mall Suite 1264Toronto, ON M9B6L3Canadaryan@striderseo.com8003148895
This website requires cookies for full functionality. By continuing to use the site, you agree to our use of cookies.
OK
